life kind of marches on tsunamis occur
生活在海啸中游行
earthquakes happen life sweeps over us
地震发生在我们身上
in literal floods and then it also feels
在字面洪水中然后它也感觉到
just like it's overwhelming us day after
就像它在我们的第二天压倒一样
day anniversaries keep coming birthdays
日纪念日不断生日
keep coming people get married friends
不断前来的人结婚的朋友
get sick loved ones die Mary's brother
生病的亲人死于玛丽的兄弟
in 2010 Rob passed away at age 65 I'm on
在2010年抢在65岁时去世，我在
my way here last night then learned that
我昨晚在这里的路上了解到了
my cousin passed away at age 64 we have
我的表哥去世的64， 我们有年龄
all kinds of heartache that is going on
各种心痛正在发生
all around us there are Wars there are
我们周围都有战争
rumors of wars there are terrorist
关于战争的谣言有恐怖分子
attacks there are suicide bombers on the
袭击中有自杀式炸弹袭击者
airlines they got bombs in their shoes
航空公司他们穿着炸弹
and they got bombs in their pants you go
并且他们在他们的裤子，你去了炸弹
to the corner supermarket just to listen
到角落超市只是为了听
to your Congressman talk about politics
你的国会议员谈论政治
and then in Arizona six people are
然后在亚利桑那州有六个人
killed and 14 are wounded stocks go up
死亡和14人受伤股票上涨
stocks go down investments fail
股票下跌投资失败
I saw the headlines in a Forbes Internet
我在福布斯互联网上看到了头条新闻
article yesterday about the real estate
昨天关于房地产的文章
bubble is gonna break and I thought it
泡沫会破裂，我想到了
had already broken actually and you know
实际上已经破了，你知道
you watched the news and you're
你看过这个消息，你就是
depressed but life keeps marching on we
郁闷但生活继续向我们迈进
lay plans and then the plans get laid
制定计划，然后制定计划
aside in the fall of 2008 Mary and I
除了2008年秋天玛丽和我
moved out of our townhouse which had 32
搬出我们32号的联排别墅
steps and every time he turned around
他每次转身都会走路
you were going up or down we thought we
你在上升或下降，我们认为我们
were mainly moving because of Mary's hip
由于玛丽的臀部 ，主要是移动
and I was having some back problems as
我有一些背部问题
well she went into the hospital to give
好吧，她进了医院给了
blood for her surgery that was to take
为她的手术采取的血液
place for a hip replacement and passed
地方髋关节置换，并通过
out had to delay her surgery but then in
out 不得不推迟她的手术，但后来
the delay for her surgery I ended up
她的手术延迟我结束了
having back surgery for a herniated disc
为椎间盘突出症做背部手术
in my back and made it to our March the
在我的背上，并使它到我们的三月
23rd of 2009 and within five weeks the
2009年 23 日和五周之内
disc had rehan
光盘有rehan
and I found myself on May 21st and what
我发现自己在5月21日和什么
is affectionately called by the dsm-4
受到dsm-4的亲切称呼
clinical depression what do you do when
临床抑郁症你做什么的时候
the counselor wakes up depressed that's
辅导员醒来郁闷这
what this is about
这是关于什么的
listen to Solomon Solomon comments on
听所罗门所罗门的评论
life in Ecclesiastes nine eleven he says
他说，在十一点的传道书中生活
again I saw Under the Sun that the race
再一次，我看到了太阳下那场比赛
is not to the Swift and the battle is
不是斯威夫特而是战斗
not to the Warriors and neither is bread
不是勇士 也不是面包
to the wise nor wealth to the discerning
聪明人，也不财富挑剔
nor favour to men of ability for time
也不喜欢有时间能力的男人
and chance catch up with everybody there
并且有机会赶上那里的每个人
it is time and chance catches up with
时间和机会赶上了
everybody you come into life screaming
每个人都会尖叫起来
bald and toothless and if you live long
秃头和无牙， 如果你长寿
enough you probably go out screaming
你可能会大声尖叫
bald and toothless
秃头无牙
but God don't you love it because the
但是上帝不喜欢它，因为
scripture is full of those expressions
经文充满了这些表达
where here's life but God where the
这里的生活，但上帝在哪里
psalmist said soul why are you in
诗人说灵魂为什么你在
despair hoping God you will again praise
绝望希望上帝你会再次赞美
him and he talks to his soul and we have
他和他谈论他的灵魂，我们有
the promise that we've been over as we
我们已经过去的承诺
talked about hope God is in all things
谈到希望上帝在万物中
he works all things together for good
他把所有的事情一起做好
here's a line from Jay Adams little book
这是Jay Adams的一本小书
you know how to handle trouble based on
你知道如何处理麻烦
Romans 8:28 it's a great resource get a
罗马书8:28这是一个很好的资源得到
hold of that one how to handle trouble
抓住那一个如何处理麻烦
by Jay Adams in terms of just dealing
由Jay Adams提供的交易方面
with life's trials and taking everything
与生活的考验和采取一切
you can out of that promise in Romans
你可以在罗马人的承诺之外
8:29 God is in your problem and he's in
8:29上帝在你的问题中，他在
it for good that's a line worth
这是好的，这是值得的
remembering God's in your problem and
在你的问题中记住上帝
he's in it for good
他很好
so life marches on time and chance
时间和机会 ，所以生活游行
overtakes everybody but God is in every
超越每个人，但上帝在每一个人
detail and he's in it for good and so we
细节，他是好的，所以我们
can trust in that the psalmist said in
可以相信诗人说的话
Psalm 77 12 I will ponder all your work
诗篇77 12 我会思考你所有的工作
and I'll meditate on your many may
我会冥想你的许多人
mighty deeds I'll ponder your works I'll
伟大的事迹我会思考你的作品我会
meditate on your mighty deeds we need to
冥想我们需要的强大行为
stop proverbs chapter 4 verse 26 says
停止箴言第4章26节说
watch the path of your feet and all your
看你的脚和你所有的路径
ways will be established there's a
将建立一种方式
sovereign God who's working all things
主权的上帝谁在做所有事情
together we need to stop we need to
同时我们需要停止，我们需要
reflect we need to ask the question and
反映我们需要问问题和
we'll talk about that much more
我们将谈论更多
afternoon in in the question well what
下午在问题以及什么
is God doing in this situation I want
是上帝在我想要的这种情况下做的
you to change gears for a moment I want
你改变齿轮片刻 我想
you to think about Elijah the prophet of
你要想到以利亚的先知 以利亚
God I want you to think about the Mount
上帝，我想让你想起山
where I experienced where he's on the
我在哪里经历过他在哪里
mountain
山
it's him against the 450 prophets of
这是他反对450的先知
Bale and they're cutting themselves
贝尔和他们正在削减自己
they're crying out to their God and he
他们向他们的上帝和他哭泣
builds the altar and he cries out to his
建立祭坛， 他大声呼喊他 的
God God answers with fire tremendous
上帝上帝以极大的火力回答
spiritual victory this man of steel this
精神上的胜利，钢铁这个人
man who is one who prays and it doesn't
是一个祈祷而不是祈祷的人
rain for three years he's a man of like
下雨三年他是一个喜欢的男人
passions according to James like we are
根据詹姆斯的激情，就像我们一样
and yet he's a righteous man and his
然而他是一个正义的人和他的
prayer avails much and he's a mighty
祈祷很有用，他是一个强大的人
prophet of God and the hand of God is on
上帝的先知和上帝的手正在上帝
him and you know when he when he stands
他和你知道他何时站立
before a hab the first time and he tells
在他第一次出现之前，他说
a hab it's not going to rain and he goes
一个hab它不会下雨而且他会去
to the brook and he hides by the brook
小溪，他在小溪边隐藏着
and the Ravens and and they bring him
乌鸦和他们带来了他
bread and meat and they provide for him
面包和肉，他们为他提供
and then there's the cruse of oil that
然后就是石油的残酷
doesn't grow dry and then there's the
不会变干然后就是了
widow's son that dies and it raises the
寡妇的儿子死了，它提出了
son from the dead and and then he gets
儿子从死里复活，然后他得到了
called to go talk to a hab again and
打电话再次和哈巴说话
this time when he stands before Ahab
这个时候，他才亚哈站
Ahab says you troubler of Israel and
亚哈说你对以色列和以色列的困扰
hell I just says I'm not the trouble or
我只是说我不是麻烦或者
vision you the trouble out of Israel and
让你远离以色列和你的麻烦
he just stands up to him and then he's
他只是站起来对他而言他是
up against 450 prophets of Bale I mean
我的意思是反对450名贝尔先知
it's a tense situation have you ever
你有没有紧张的局面
been in a situation where even just you
在一个甚至只是你的情况下
got one co-worker and you know they just
有一个同事，你知道他们只是
plain don't agree with you and every
平原不同意你和每一个人
time you suggest something they suggest
时间你提出好的建议，他们建议
the opposite and it's like oh that's
相反，它就像是哦
tense but imagine mean I'm up against
紧张但想象意味着我反对
450 prophets of Bale you're the only one
罢了 450名先知你是唯一一个
who's standing up for God and know
谁站起来为上帝而且知道
you're gonna build the altar well that's
你要去建造祭坛嗯，这是
you know and you so you're gonna put the
你知道的，所以你要把它放进去
animal on the altar and then you're
在祭坛上的动物，然后你
gonna build a trench or dig a trench
要建一个沟槽或挖沟
around the altar and then you pour on
在祭坛周围然后你倒了
buckets of water till is running off the
水桶一直在运行
altar and running in the trough and run
祭坛， 在低谷中奔跑并奔跑
it down and then you just pray this
它下来然后你只是祈祷
short brief little prayer you know okay
简短的小祷告，你知道好吗
God send fire
上帝送火
and God sends fire and then you oversee
上帝发火，然后你监督
the execution of all those prophets then
然后执行所有这些先知
in you run a marathon 26 miles into town
在你跑进 城里26英里的马拉松比赛
I mean this guy is some guy so the next
我的意思是这个家伙是下一个人
day Jezebel is saying to a hab you know
耶洗别对你知道的哈哈说
you send a message to that prophet you
你向先知发信息给你
tell him I'll make him toast like he
告诉他我会让他像他一样敬酒
made my prophets toast and you're just
让我的先知敬酒，你只是
waiting ha ha
等哈哈
what's the prophet of Steel gonna say
什么是钢铁的先知会说
this time and the text says and he ran
这一次，文字说，他跑了
for his life what you know this is the
对于他的生活你知道这是什么
Word of God
神的话语
and what's it tell us in the Word of God
它在神的话语中告诉我们什么
first corinthians 10:6 now these things
哥林多前书10：6现在这些事
happen as examples for us so that we
作为我们的例子发生在我们身上
would not crave evil things as they
他们不会渴望邪恶的东西
craved you know do not be idolaters as
渴望你知道不要成为偶像崇拜者
some of those were who the people sat
其中一些是人民坐的
down to eat and drink and stood up to
吃下来，喝，站起身来
play you know nor let us act immorally
玩你知道也不让我们行动起来
as some of them did 23000 fell in one
因为他们中的一些人做了23000倒在一个
day don't grumble like some of them did
一天不要像他们中的一些人那样发牢骚
and were destroyed by the destroyer
并被驱逐舰摧毁
again now these things happen to them as
现在这些事情发生在他们身上了
an example and they were written for our
一个例子，他们是为我们写的
instruction upon those who whom the end
指示那些结束的人
of the age of come therefore let him who
因此来到他的身上
thinks he stands fast take heed that he
认为他站得很快就注意到了他
does not fall no temptation has
不会没有诱惑
overtaken you but such as is common to
取代你，但是很常见
man why are all these things recorded in
男人为什么要记录所有这些东西
the Old Testament for our instruction
我们教导的旧约
why we have the life of Elijah why does
为什么我们有以利亚的生命为什么呢
it tell us that there was a situation
它告诉我们有一种情况
when Elijah didn't say you troubler of
当以利亚没有说你烦恼的时候
Israel where he got up and ran for his
以色列他站起来为他奔跑
life what happened here what changed the
生活在这里发生了什么改变了
circumstances our temptations our common
情况我们的诱惑是我们共同的
problems God's faithful God won't allow
上帝的忠诚上帝不会允许的问题
you to be tempted beyond what you are
你被诱惑超越自己
able depression is a common problem
抑郁症是一个常见的问题
listen to this quote from Newsweek cover
听新闻周刊封面报道
story back in February of 2007 6 million
故事早在2007年2月就有600万
American men will be diagnosed with
美国男性将被诊断出患有此病
depression this year but millions more
今年萧条但数百万
suffer silently unaware that their
他们默默地不知道他们的
problem has a name or are unwilling to
问题有名或不愿意
seek treatment as an assistant editor
寻求治疗作为助理编辑
Julie Scialfa reports this men and
Julie Scialfa报道了这个男人和女人
depression she says although depression
抑郁症她说尽管抑郁症
is emotionally crippling and has
是情绪影响巨大，有
numerous medical implication
众多医学意义
some of them deadly many men fail to
他们中的一些致命的许多人都没有
recognize the symptoms instead of
认识到症状而不是
talking about their feelings men may
谈论他们的感情男人可能
mask them with alcohol drugs abuse drug
用酒精药物滥用药物掩盖它们
abuse or gambling or anger or by
虐待或赌博或愤怒或通过
becoming workaholics and even when they
成为工作狂，即使他们
do realize they have a problem men often
确实意识到他们经常遇到问题
view asking for help as an admission of
寻求帮助作为承认
weakness one of the men who came to sit
弱者中有一个来坐的人
with me when I was depressed he actually
我当我是真的 郁闷，他
thought he was sitting with me because
以为他和我在一起是因为
of my back problem because I was still
我的背部问题，因为我还在
recovering from the back surgery he
他从背部手术中恢复过来
didn't know he was sitting with me
不知道他和我坐在一起
because my wife needed some time away
因为我的妻子需要一些时间
from me and they didn't want we home
来自我，他们不希望我们回家
alone because I had been having suicidal
因为我一直有自杀倾向
thoughts so you know if you're walking
想法， 所以你知道你是否走路
with that situation you have people
在那种情况下，你有人
there and so he was there for that
在那里，所以他就在那里
purpose and you know as I was talking to
目的，你知道我在说话
him I ended up telling him that I was
他我最后告诉他我是
depressed and they said well Bob that's
郁闷，他们说好了鲍勃
really nothing you know I was depressed
真的没什么，你知道我很沮丧
he said for a whole year he said every
他说了一整年他都说了
day on the way home I kept in my car an
回家的路上，我在车里 待了一天
old sweatshirt and every day on the way
旧运动衫，每天都在路上
home from LA he worked he was living at
来自洛杉矶的家，他住在那里
that time up in the Lancaster area he
在兰开斯特面积时间长达他
said I would soak that sweatshirt with
说我会泡是运动衫
my tears soak it and then I said I would
我的眼泪浸透了它，然后我说我愿意
pull the car over before I got home and
在我回到家之前把车拉过来
I tell him suck it up I go in the house
我告诉他，我去了房子
I said well did you talk to anybody at
我说得好，你跟谁说话了
shirt now they wouldn't understand then
衬衫现在他们就不会那么理解
one didn't know what I was going through
一个人不知道我经历了什么
and he didn't talk about it and the
他没有谈论它和
result according to this article is that
根据这篇文章的结果是
they say the result is a hidden epidemic
他们说结果是一种隐藏的流行病
of despair that's destroying marriages
绝望，这是破坏婚姻
disrupting careers filling jail cells
破坏职业填补监狱牢房
clogging emergency rooms costing society
堵塞急诊室耗费社会
billions of dollars in lost productivity
数十亿美元的生产力损失
and medical bills it's creating a cohort
和医疗费用它创造了一个队列
of children who carry the burden of
承担责任的儿童
their father's pain for the rest of
他们的父亲的痛苦的休息
their lives our definition of a
他们的生活是我们的定义
successful man in this culture does not
这种文化中成功的人没有
include being depressed or down or sad
包括沮丧，沮丧或悲伤
in many ways it's the exact opposite a
在许多方面，它恰恰相反
successful man is always up he's always
成功的男人始终是他总是
positive he's always in charge he's in
积极的，他总是掌控着他
control of his emotions in the Evangelic
控制 他在福音中的情感
Oliva touch you know spiritually mature
奥利瓦触摸你知道灵性成熟
men aren't depressed
男人不沮丧
successful pastors are depressed people
成功的牧师是郁闷的人
who teach biblical counseling at the
谁教导圣经辅导
Masters College are not depressed but
大师学院并不沮丧，但
what about Martin Luther what about
关于马丁·路德什么什么
Charles Spurgeon what about John Owen
查尔斯司布真怎么样约翰欧文
what about copper those men all dealt
那些男人都处理过的铜怎么样？
with depression Cowper went out of his
抑郁症Cowper离开了他的
life still going through those
生活还在经历那些
depression cycles it was John Newton the
抑郁症周期是John Newton
writer of the great hymn Amazing Grace
伟大的赞美诗格雷斯格雷斯的作家
who stuck with copper through all those
谁通过所有这些坚持铜
times but it's Cowper who writes
写的是考珀
tremendous hymns that you have sung and
你已经唱赞美诗巨大 和
so what do you do with that there's a
那么你有什么用呢？
book I just mentioned this one's
我刚刚提到过这本书
depression is stubborn darkness by Ed
艾德沮丧是顽固的黑暗
Welch and in that book he writes this
韦尔奇在那本书中写道
the caretaker of the technical language
技术语言的看护人
for depression is the American
抑郁症是美国人
Psychiatric Association and it's
精神病学协会和它的
diagnostic manual it's called the
诊断手册它被称为
Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of
诊断和统计手册
Mental Disorders it's in its fourth
精神障碍是第四次
edition they're trying to put out a
他们试图推出一个版本
fifth one now but they're getting
现在排名第五，但他们已经到了
problems with themselves on that but
他们自己的问题但是
listen to this this is how it reads five
听听这就是 五读
five or more of the following nine
以下九个中的五个或更多
symptoms five or more of the following
症状五种或更多以下
nine symptoms present during the same
在同一期间出现九种症状
two-week period representing a change
代表变化的两周时间
from previous functioning and at least
从以前的功能和至少
one of the symptoms is either depressed
其中一个症状是抑郁症
mood or the loss of interest or pleasure
情绪或失去兴趣或愉悦
and if you've got five or Morlan than
如果你有五个或莫兰比
your clinically depressed so on May the
你的临床沮丧所以就五月了
21st I'm laying on the couch we are now
21我躺在沙发上，我们现在
living not in our townhouse we've moved
生活在我们的联排别墅里，我们已经搬走了
out of the townhouse we're living in a
走出联排别墅，我们住在一个
600 square foot apartment we plan to be
600 平方英尺的公寓，我们计划 成为
in there for a couple of months for Mary
玛丽在那里待了几个月
surgery before we would find a new home
手术之前我们会找到一个新家
we ended up being there a year and a
我们结束了 一年 在那里
half but the day before mary has said to
一半，但玛丽说的前一天
me I remember had my surgery in March
我记得三月份做过手术
then a rehearing Aidid disc all that
然后重新审理艾迪德盘全部
stuff going on she said to me the day
正在发生的事情她说那天
before May the 28th I remember the day
在5月28日之前，我记得那一天
because it was her birthday she said Bob
因为这是她的生日，她说鲍勃
you are depressed I am not depressed
你很沮丧，我并不沮丧
you know and I got upset by that you
你知道，我为你感到沮丧
know I'm a biblical counsellor I'm a
知道我是一个圣经辅导员我是
pastor no I'm not depressed you know you
牧师不，我不郁闷，你认识你
can call me some of those other names
可以叫我其他一些名字
it's okay but not depressed but I picked
它没关系，但没有沮丧，但我选择了
up the book and I decided to reread and
这本书，我决定重读和
as I'm reading I read this page number
正如我正在读的那样， 我读了这个页码
one depressed mood most of the day
一天大部分时间情绪低落
nearly every day is indicated by either
几乎每一天都由两者表示
subjective report feels sad or empty or
主观报告感到悲伤或空洞或
observation made by others appears
他人的观察出现了
tearful my wife knew I was depressed
我妻子知道我很沮丧
David Gabriel the elder in our church
大卫加布里埃尔是我们教会的长老
who was working with me knew I was
和我一起工作的人都知道我是
depressed and I thought you know nearly
郁闷，我以为你几乎知道
every day do I have a depressed mood yes
我每天都有抑郁的情绪
markedly diminished interest or pleasure
显着减少的兴趣或乐趣
in all or almost all activities most of
在所有或几乎所有活动中
the day nearly every day I can I can
我几乎每天都能做到这一天
tell you that during this time period I
告诉你， 在这段时间里我
had no pleasure in anything
什么都不高兴
nothing was pleasureful I would watch a
没什么好看的我会看
movie that I used to think was fun I
电影， 我曾经以为 是我的乐趣
like the program monk I would watch monk
像节目僧人我会看和尚
and say I used to laugh at that now it's
并说我现在笑了， 现在就是这样
serious I feel like I am monk
严重我觉得我是和尚
and I don't like that feeling at all all
我不喜欢这种感觉，在所有的一切
right
对
significant weight loss when dieting or
节食或减肥时体重明显减轻
weight gain a change of more than five
体重增加超过五
percent in body weight in a month or a
一个月或一个 体重的百分比
decrease or an increase in the appetite
减少或增加食欲
between January of onine and June of oh
在onine和June的1月之间哦
nine I lost 50 pounds and I wasn't
九，我减掉了50磅，而我却没有
dieting people would say pop you look
节食的人会说你看起来流行
good and I think I may look good to you
很好，我想我可能看起来很好
I don't feel good and if you want to
如果你愿意，我感觉不舒服
know a diet plan you don't want this one
知道你不想要这个饮食计划
I just had no appetite I only ate
我只是没有胃口我只吃了
because I knew God would have me to eat
因为我知道上帝会让我吃
and take care of my body portions I ate
并照顾我吃的身体部位
Mary would say you that's all you're
玛丽会说你就是这样
eating and I ate because she fixed it
吃饭，我吃了，因为她修好了
and she fixed healthy things and I
她固定了健康的东西和我
wanted to you know please her I ate but
我想知道她，我吃了但是
only that way insomnia or hypersomnia
只有那样失眠或睡眠过度
nearly every day I couldn't sleep
几乎每天我都无法入睡
psychomotor agitation or retardation
精神运动激动或迟钝
what in the world is that
这个世界是什么
well I knew what it was it's this you
我知道这就是你的意思
know and nervousness and clasping your
知道和紧张，并紧握你的
hands and unclasping your hand and I had
我伸手握住你的手
to sit and kind of grip my knees in
坐下来， 有点夹紧我的膝盖
order to stop doing what I knew I was
为了停止做我知道的事情
doing when I was with people fatigue or
当我和人一起疲惫时，我正在做什么
loss of energy nearly every day I would
我几乎每天都会失去能量
stare at the computer to pretend I was
盯着电脑假装我是
doing something and not do anything I
做某事而不做任何我
can correct a tank exam usually in
通常可以纠正坦克考试
approximately three hours it would take
需要大约三个小时
me three days and I would stare at the
我三天，我会盯着看
computer again just to look like I was
电脑又只是看起来像我
doing something and I would also do that
做某事我也会这样做
to avoid having to talk to people
以避免与人交谈
feelings of worthlessness or excessive
无价值或过度的感觉
or inappropriate guilt nearly every day
或几乎每天都有不恰当的内疚感
I believed I would never teach again I
我相信我永远不会再教我了
believed I would never preach again I
相信我再也不会传教了
believed I would never be able to learn
相信我永远无法学习
at living again I believed that we would
在生活中， 我相信我们会
live out the rest of our days in my
在我的余生中度过余生
brothers in-laws basement apartment it's
兄弟在法律地下室公寓很
a nice basement apartment but it's not
一个不错的地下室公寓，但事实并非如此
the way I expected to spend the rest of
我期望花费其余时间的方式
my life but I was convinced at that time
我的生活，但我相信在那个时候
that that's what was going to happen I
这就是我将要发生的事情
did not think I would ever teach again I
没想到我会再教我一次
was told by friends that I would I was
有朋友告诉我，我会的
told by Ernie Baker who was taking a
厄尼贝克告诉他
lead role in counseling me that I would
在我的咨询中担任主角
you'll hear
你会听到的
earning this afternoon as one of our
今天下午作为我们的一员 赚钱
speakers for today diminished ability to
今天的发言者减少了能力
think or concentrate I've already told
思考或集中我已经说过了
you about that recurrent thoughts of
关于那些经常性的想法
death recurrent suicidal ideation
死亡反复出现的自杀意念
without specific plan or a suicide
没有具体计划或自杀
attempt or a specific plan for
尝试或具体计划
committing suicide the symptoms are not
自杀的症状不是
due to the direct physiological effects
由于直接的生理影响
of a substance like drug abuse or no
滥用药物或不吸毒的物质
medication now I do think that the
药物现在我确实认为
medications that I was on for pain had
我因疼痛而服用的药物
some things to do with what was
有些事情与之相关
happening but the fact is I don't know
发生但事实是我不知道
on all of that but I can tell you this I
所有这一切，但我可以告诉你我
walk down the sidewalk and I would think
沿着人行道走，我想
about stepping out in front of the
关于走出前面
trucks that would go by and timing it so
卡车会过去并计时
that I could be sure that they had hit
我可以肯定他们已经击中了
me hard enough to kill me because I
我很难杀死我，因为我
certainly didn't want to maim myself and
当然不想残害自己，
then I would think you don't even
然后我会认为你甚至没有
believe you're saved right now if you're
相信如果你是的话，你现在就得救了
not saved you know where you're going if
没有救你知道你要去哪里
you step in front of the truck
您在卡车前面步骤
and even in my depression I could think
甚至在我的沮丧中我能想到
this doesn't make sense
这没有意义
I thought about driving the car up the
我想过要开车了
freeway and then just pulling it across
高速公路，然后只是把它拉过来
the middle lane into the line of an
中间车道进入一条线
18-wheeler coming in the other direction
18轮到另一个方向
that ought to do the job then I thought
那应该做的工作然后我想
yeah but what about if the 18-wheeler
是的，但如果18轮车怎么样
guy doesn't want to go at that time oh
那个家伙当时不想去哦
and what about if he swerves his car and
如果他转向他的车怎么样呢？
he hits somebody else now these are the
他现在打了别人， 这些都是
things I would have told somebody else
我会告诉别人的事情
telling me those thoughts I knew how to
告诉我那些我知道如何的想法
counsel suicidal people but I never
律师自杀， 但我从来没有
expected to be in that boat and I could
预计将在船上和我可以
give you a lot more of that kind of
给你更多的 那样的
stuff so I'm reading this and it's made
东西，所以我正在读这个，它已经成型
of twenty first and I wrote in the
我先写了二十分
margin this is me and I thought how did
边缘这是我，我想怎么做
I get here
我到了
I think Elijah under the broom tree also
我认为Elijah也在扫帚树下
woke up and said how did I get here he
醒了，说我怎么到这里来的
says to God Lord I don't want to live
对上帝说， 我不想活着
just take me home I'm no better than the
带我回家我不比
other prophets
其他先知
just take me out now let's think about
现在让我考虑一下吧
it how do you develop a severe case of
你怎么发展一个严重的情况
depression all right well I think the
抑郁症没事好，我觉得
factor that we see in the life of Elijah
我们在以利亚的生活中看到的因素
and we're going to move quickly as we
而且我们会像我们一样迅速行动
work through these things we're gonna
我们将通过这些工作
work through this rapidly fear of men
通过这项 工作 迅速害怕的男人
rather than fear of God you believe the
而不是上帝的敬畏你相信
circumstances rather than God's promises
环境而不是上帝的承诺
what does Elijah do in this situation
在这种情况下 ，以利亚做了什么
well God has worked on the mountain God
上帝已经在山神上工作了
has worked amazingly God has worked
上帝的工作令人惊讶
powerfully and now Jezebel is sending
有力而且现在耶洗别正在派遣
him a message and the message is I'm
他是一条消息，而且消息是我
gonna get you you would think she would
会得到你， 你会认为她会
have thought soon maybe it's not a wise
很快就想到也许这不是明智之举
to get him the 450 prophets are all dead
得到他的450位先知都死了
so I don't think Elijah comprehends the
所以我不认为以利亚理解这一点
physical and emotional strain that he's
他的身体和情绪紧张
been living under Elijah probably
大概生活在以利亚之下
doesn't see the results he was hoping
没有看到他希望的结果
for a lasting revival he's hoping that a
为了持久的复兴，他希望能有一个
hab would fully turnaround that Jezebel
哈布完全扭转了耶洗别的局面
would turn around but the answer isn't
会转过身，但答案却不是
is that he now runs for his life and so
是他现在为他的生命而奔波
in that running for his life what is he
为了他的生命，他的生命是什么
doing well he's neglecting the place of
做得好，他忽略了
his duty if see as you read back through
如果您在回顾过程中看到他的职责
the context of these chapters you see
你看到这些章节的背景
God says hey bruh
上帝说嘿嘿
I'll add you does God says I'll add you
我会补充你，上帝说我会加你
to us God says Elisha does God says
我们说神不以利沙说上帝
Elisha does and God's hand is on him now
以利沙确实和上帝的手现在在他身上
he doesn't ask he just runs for his life
他并没有要求他只为自己的生命而奔波
and so in that context he's running for
所以在那种背景下，他正在竞选
his life
他的生命
he's afraid what he should have done is
他担心他应该做的是什么
what declared his trust in God and gone
什么宣称他对上帝的信任而消失了
to God with direction and it's very
向上帝指示方向，而且非常
possible God might have said to him flee
可能上帝可能对他说过逃跑
when he first gave the prayer of the the
当他第一次给出了祈祷的时候
message to a hab what does God say to
向上帝说出了什么信息
him to do go up by the brook Zarafa and
他做的小溪Zarafa而上
you out of the brook and hide yourself
你走出小溪，隐藏自己
and I'll have the Ravens feed you God
我会让乌鸦喂你神
directs him to get out of town
指示他要离开 这个城市，
not to stick around so Ahab can take out
不要留下来让亚哈可以拿出来
his rap on him but in this case he
他对他说唱， 但在这种情况下，他
neglects his place of duty and because
忽略了他的职责，因为
he's afraid and he runs not for the
他害怕，他不是为了这个
glory of God and not to help people but
神的荣耀，而不是帮助人，但
for his life the day before he runs for
在他竞选前一天的生活
the glory of God he outruns the chariot
上帝的荣耀，他就是战车
to town the guys in shape
这个家伙的形状
he runs a marathon it's about 26 miles
他跑马拉松大约26英里
that he ran the day before but now he's
他前一天跑了，但现在他跑了
not running for his glory God's glory
不为他的荣耀而奔跑上帝的荣耀
and we read you know and you can look up
我们读你知道了，你可以抬头看看
you've got in your notes all these
你已经记下了所有这些
references you can check them out how
参考，你可以检查他们如何
the hand of God was on him where he was
上帝的手在他所在的地方
but now he doesn't run for the glory of
但现在他并没有为了荣耀而奔跑
God he neglects his place of Duty leaves
上帝他忽略了他的职责离开的 地方
where he was which was the pattern of
他是哪个模式
his life up to this point and he runs
他的生活到了这一步，他跑了
for his life people who are depressed
他的生活中， 人们谁是郁闷
many times have neglected their duty
很多时候都忽略了他们的职责
they've stopped doing what they need to
他们已经停止做他们需要什么
do and you need to realize that one of
做，你需要意识到这一点
the worst things you might do for a
你可能做的最糟糕的事情
person who's depressed is to take all
沮丧的人就是全力以赴
responsibility away from them I had to
责任远离他们，我不得不
stop doing almost everything I was done
停止做我做的几乎所有事情
but I still corrected bank exams I still
但我仍然纠正了银行考试
did what I could do in terms of
做了什么，我可以在以下方面做
directing those that filled in for me
指导那些为我填补的
while I took a semester off from my
我从学期开始学了一个学期
duties and they were adjunct professors
职责，他们是兼职教授
and I gave them an a console as to what
我给了他们一个关于什么的控制台
they could do in that situation
他们可以在那种情况下做
but be sure that you balance that with
但要确保你 与之平衡
the need for rest you're gonna see that
需要休息，你会看到
in a couple of minutes so what happens
在几分钟内发生了什么
in this situation that leads into the
在这种情况下，导致进入
depression people who are depressed have
抑郁症患者有抑郁症
stopped doing their duty but the next
停止履行职责但下一步
thing is neglect your physical needs you
事情是忽视你的身体需要你
see I want you to think about this
见我希望你想想这个
Elijah was mentally and physically
以利亚是精神上和身体上的
exhausted how does this man of steel in
筋疲力尽的这个男人是怎么回事的
the center of God's will wake up under
上帝的中心会被唤醒
the juniper tree suicidally depressed
杜松树自杀郁闷
think about this there's the emotional
想想这就是情感
tension of confronting the king in 17:1
17：1对抗国王的紧张局势
there's the emotional stress of living
有生活的情感压力
under hand-to-mouth conditions there's
在口对口的条件下
the Brooke there's the widow of
布鲁克那里有寡妇
Zarephath being fed by the Ravens
Zarephath 由乌鸦喂养
having to
不必
tell her that that the cruse of oil and
告诉她，石油巡航和
the flour won't run dry there's the
面粉不会干涸还有的
emotional stress of the extraordinary
非凡的情绪压力
call to ministry when the widow's son
寡妇的儿子，请求传道
die who gets blamed
谁受到责备谁死了
Elijah gets blamed there's the emotional
以利亚被归咎于那种情绪
stress of living under the threat of
下的 威胁下生活的压力
death you know you've got somebody
死，你知道你有人
looking for you to kill you
找你杀了你
according to at first Kings 1813 there's
根据在第一次国王1813有
the emotional tension of confronting the
面对的 情绪紧张
king again he has to go down he has to
国王，他必须下去，他必须
confront the king and the King says to
面对国王和国王说
him is this you you troubler of Israel
他是你，你是以色列的困扰者
and he says no I'm not troubled as
他说不，我不会感到困扰
really you have and you and your
真的，你和你，你
father's house there's the emotional
父亲的房子里有情感
tension of confronting the prophets of
面对先知的紧张
bale up on the mountain you know you
在你了解你的山上打包
know the situation how emotional it is
知道情况是怎么样的情感
with one fellow employee who doesn't
一个同事的员工谁不
agree with you but it's 450 to one
同意你，但它是450比1
there's the emotional tension of waiting
等待 的情绪紧张
for God to answer with fire and the
因为上帝用火来回答
building of the altar the flaying of the
建筑的祭坛剥落了
animal the pouring on the water the
动物浇在水面上
tremendous emotion of that situation
这种情况的巨大情绪
there's no record in the text of Elijah
有以利亚的文本没有记录
ever stopping to eat that day the
那天停下来吃饭了
emotional joy of seeing revival in
看到复兴的情感快乐
Israel
以色列
you know the people say oh the Lord he
你知道人们说主啊他
is God when God sends the fire the Lord
当上帝将火赐给主时，就是上帝
he is God there's the emotional tension
他是上帝的情绪紧张
of overseeing the execution the 450
监督450的执行
prophets of bale think about it if you
如果你，贝尔的先知会考虑它
had to pull a switch on the electric
不得不拉开电动开关
here 450 times in one day you think that
这里在一天 450次 你认为
would be emotional let's read a book
情绪化让我们读一本书
about the death penalty I happen to
关于死刑我碰巧
believe the Scriptures teach the death
相信圣经教导死亡
penalty he execute the death penalty 450
罚款他执行死刑450
prophets a day they'll die that day
有一天先知他们会在那天死去
then there's the emotional tension of
然后是情绪紧张
praying again for rain and he's waiting
再次祈祷下雨，他正在等待
for the answers sending this prophet
发送这位先知的答案
back in for his servant back and forth
回来为他的仆人来回
and everything depends on your prayer
一切都取决于你的祷告
then there's the physical exhaustion of
然后是身体疲惫
running a marathon ever talk to somebody
跑马拉松的人跟别人说话
the day after they run a marathon
他们参加马拉松比赛的第二天
I feel really down and you know um
我觉得很失落，你知道嗯
the day after can be really bad and so
以后的日子可真不好 等
the question is was Elijah directly in
问题是以利亚直接进入
the center of God's will answer yes but
上帝的中心会回答是，但是
I believe he is emotionally and
我相信他是情绪化的
physically exhausted you need to be sure
身体疲惫你需要确定
that as you're dealing with people that
，当你要处理的人们，
you recognize that they may have
你认识到他们可能有
neglected their own physical needs and
忽视了自己的身体需求和
gotten in that or they may have been in
得到了或他们可能已经进入
the center of God's will doing all that
神的旨意中心尽一切
they thought they should be doing and
他们认为他们应该这样做
that still occurred okay
仍然发生好吗
first sign could be significant sleep
第一个迹象可能是重要的睡眠
loss and the first sign of significant
损失和重要的第一个迹象
sleep loss is irritability most
睡眠不足是最烦躁的
Americans live on the razor's edge of
美国人生活在剃刀的边缘
irritability all the time because they
一直都很烦躁， 因为他们
let the TV determine when they go to bed
让电视决定他们什么时候上床睡觉
just record the program and watch it the
只记录程序并观看它
next night early in the evening and you
晚上第二天晚上早，你
can avoid all the commercials it's great
可以避免它的所有商业广告
you know now think about it you forget
你知道现在想想你忘了
to seek the guidance of the Lord as well
也寻求主的指导
and so we have all of that but at this
所以我们拥有所有这一切，但就此而言
point and this juncture this man of God
这个关键点和这个神的人
forgets to do it he doesn't do it he
忘记这样做，他没有这样做
just in that circumstance runs for his
只是在那种情况下为他而战
life and so at that point he doesn't
生活等等，他没有
pray he just runs now again if he prayed
如果他祈祷，他祈祷他现在再次奔跑
I think God would have said you need to
我想上帝会说你需要
break why because when God councils him
打破原因，因为当上帝委员会他
under the juniper tree the first thing
在杜松树下第一件事
God does is give him a break but he
上帝确实给了他一个休息但是他
doesn't ask and so do that I think I
我不这么想，所以我想
come in my office just this week and I
就在这个星期和我来到我的办公室
mean he's in tears he's broken now he
意味着他已经流泪了，他现在已经破碎了
hasn't had anything to eat all day and
整天都没有吃东西
he didn't sleep well the night before
他前一天晚上睡不着觉
because of the dream he had I told him a
因为他告诉他 的梦想
home and get a good meal and get a good
回家吃饭，好好吃
night's rest I don't know whether he did
晚上休息我不知道他是否做到了
that or not because someone else was
那还是不要因为别人 是
supposed to be following up on that
应该跟进
situation so but that's the idea then
情况如此，那就是那个想法
the next thing that people do in their
人们在他们身上做的下一件事
depression whoops
抑郁症呐喊
yes where are we here you know again God
是的我们在这里你再次认识上帝
asks him when he later in the chapter
他在本章后面问他
what are you doing here
你在这里做什么
when the widow's son died you have the
当寡妇的儿子去世时，你就有了
example that Elijah sought advice and
以利亚寻求建议的例子
again God might have directed him to
上帝可能再次指示他
flee the next thing people do leading in
逃离人们领导的下一件事
the depression is pray according to your
抑郁症是根据你的 祈祷
feelings Lord take me home I'm the only
感觉主带我回家我是唯一的
one left
一个人离开了
just wipe me out he's praying according
刚擦我出去根据他祈祷
to his feelings right and it's really
对他的感情是对的，这是真的
inconsistent because if he had really
不一致， 因为如果他真的
wanted that he could have stayed where
希望他能留在那里
he was and Jezebel would have done it
他和杰泽贝尔会做到这一点
see well I can testify to this when
看得好，我可以证明这一点
you're in the emotional state that
你在情感状态
you're in when you're depressed you're
当你沮丧的时候，你就在
not thinking straight and you do I
不直接思考，你做我
prayed over and over again they wanted
他们想要一遍又一遍地祈祷
me to have a second surgery I'm praying
我要做第二次手术，我在祈祷
yes let's have the second surgery and
是的让我们进行第二次手术
Lord let me die on the table you know
主让我死在你知道的桌子上
just to put me to sleep in them and
只是为了让我睡在他们身上
never wake up but in the in consisting
永远不会醒来，但在组成
of that I didn't believe I was saved I
那我不相信我得救我
believe I lost my salvation I how can
相信我失去了我的救赎我怎么能
anybody think these thoughts these
任何人都认为这些想法
suicidal thoughts these depressed
这些沮丧的自杀念头
thoughts I'm thinking and be saved I
思考我正在思考并得到拯救我
must stop lost my salvation I must not
我必须停止失去救恩
have been among the elect and you know
已经成为选民之一，你知道
you're doing I think everything gets
你在做我认为一切都会好起来的
colored by that grid of that depression
被那个凹陷的网格着色
and that you were in and instead of
并且你在而不是
praying according to the promises of God
按照上帝的应许祷告
he prays Lord take my life and it's
他祈求上帝把我的生命，它的
totally inconsistent but we should be
完全不一致，但我们应该
praying according to the promises of God
按照上帝的应许祷告
those like Isaiah 40:31 to rest in him
那些像以赛亚书40:31在他身上休息的人
and like first John 5:14 you pray
并且像约翰福音5:14那样祷告
according to the Word of God not
根据 神的话语不
according to your feelings and then the
根据你的感受然后
next thing he does he rejects his
接下来他做了什么他拒绝了他的
Christian Fellowship he goes 80 miles
基督徒团契他走了80英里
out in the wilderness then he leaves his
在荒野中然后他离开了他的
his assistant and he goes on further by
他的助手和他继续前进
himself you neglect well I didn't want
你自己疏忽我不想要
to go to church go to church people say
去教堂去教堂的人说
how you doing Bob and you know you're
你怎么做鲍勃，你知道你
supposed to say fine or good you know
应该说，罚款还是不错的，你知道
and you feel like dirt and you feel like
你感觉像是泥土，你感觉像
taking your life and you don't feel like
夺走你的生命，你感觉不到
life is worth living and everything
生命是值得的生活和一切
you're thinking is negative and you
你的想法是消极的，你
don't want to be there anyways and you
不想再和你在一起
know you
知道你
you'd want to be there to worship God
你想在那里敬拜上帝
because I mean after all you have been a
因为我的意思是你毕竟是一个
pastor for 35 years and you've been a
牧师35年，你一直是个
biblical counseling teacher for the last
圣经辅导老师为最后一位
three years and you know pretty much
三年，你知道的很多
what you should say but when they say
什么你应该说，但他们说
how are you doing you want to say I feel
你是怎么做的，你想说我觉得
like dirt how do you feel but you know
像泥土你感觉怎么样，但你知道
you also at least I still had enough
你还至少我还够受够了
sense not to say that but then I don't
感觉不是说，但我没有
want to lie and say I feel fine when I
我想撒谎说我感觉很好
don't feel fine at all and I don't want
感觉不好，我不想要
to talk to you and I don't want you
跟你说话，我不要你
asking me these questions because I
问我这些问题，因为我
don't want to have to think about how
不想考虑怎么做
I'm gonna respond so you reject
我会回应所以你拒绝
fellowship and you stay away or you make
团契，你远离或你做
a decision I'm going anyways so I made a
决定我要去，所以我做了一个
decision - please go 9 - please my 1 if
决定- 请去9- 请我的1如果
I would go to church that's what the
我会去教堂那是什么的
Word of God says you do not neglect the
神的话语说，你不要忽视
Fellowship of the assembling of yourself
自己组装的团契
together so you do that out of obedience
在一起， 所以你出于顺从而这样做
not because you feel like it Martin
不是因为你觉得像马丁
Luther in his depression would go and
路德在他的沮丧中会去
pray play hymns sometimes but in the
祈祷有时候会播放赞美诗， 但是
middle of one of his depressions
他的一个沮丧中间
according to the account I read Katie
根据我读凯蒂的帐户
came in and she's all dressed in black
走了进来，她都穿着黑色
and Martin says Katie who died and Katie
而马丁说凯蒂死了，凯蒂
said Martin God has died Martin the
说马丁上帝已经死了马丁
reformer reacted to that what do you
改革者对你做了什么反应
mean that's blasphemy how can you say
意味着亵渎你怎么能说
God has died and she said Martin you are
上帝已经死了，她说马丁是你
acting like God died then he got the
表现得像上帝死了然后他得到了
point when you are in depression you
当你陷入沮丧的时候
need fellowship and you need those that
需要团契，你需要那些
will speak the truth into your life in
会在你的生活中说出真相
love but will speak that truth to you
爱， 但会向你说出这个真理
because it is the truth of God's Word
因为这是神话语 的真理
the promises of God's Word you know he
你知道的上帝话语的应许
traveled 100 miles he was all alone and
走了100英里， 他独自一人
when you're depressed you've got to have
当你沮丧时，你必须拥有
oh and the Word of God tells us
哦，狗屎和神的话语告诉我们
seek Him and you will find him and then
寻求他，你会找到他然后
again in depression you don't take time
再次陷入萧条，你不需要时间
to get your facts straight in fact no
让你的事实直没有事实
matter what you think about the facts
重要的是你对事实的看法
they don't come out right you see
你看，他们没有出来
everything through the grid of that fog
一切都通过那雾的网格
of the depression that you are in at
你所处的抑郁症
that time and he says to himself while
那个时候，他对自己说
he's under the broom tree you know I'm
他在扫帚树下你知道我是谁
all alone I'm the only one left but
独自一人，我是唯一一个离开的人
first of all he listens to Jezebel's
首先， 他听耶洗别的
threat he hasn't been doing that no I am
威胁他没有这样做，不是我
NOT the troubler of Israel he had you
他不是以色列的麻烦者
are that's the fact
这是事实
Jezebel makes the threat look if you
如果你，耶洗别会让威胁看起来
know if she could make the threat she
知道她是否能成为她的威胁
would do it
会这样做的
she's just fuming she's like that I used
她只是发脾气，就像我用过的那样
to like watching The Lone Ranger growing
喜欢看The Lone Ranger的成长
up you know and I loved it because you
你了解我喜欢它，因为你
know the bad guy would catch The Lone
知道坏人会抓住The Lone
Ranger and then the bad guy would be
游侠，然后是坏人
talking about what he's gonna do to him
谈论他将对他做些什么
and I would be sitting there thinking
而我会坐在那里思考
just shoot him because if you don't
只是射击他，因为如果你不这样做
shoot him Tonto is gonna come and rescue
射击他Tonto会来救援
him these outlaws are so stupid you know
他知道，这些歹徒是如此愚蠢
you know and I didn't really want them
你知道，我真的不想要他们
to shoot him but I'm just thinking they
射杀他，但我只是在想他们
are so dumb and you see Jezebel sounding
是如此愚蠢，你看到耶洗别听起来
off but you know if you're depressed you
但你知道你是否感到沮丧
don't get the facts straight I'm the
没有得到澄清事实，我的
only one left what does God tell him
只有一个离开了上帝告诉他的东西
later when God gives him the straight
后来， 当上帝给他直
stuff there's 7,000 Bob that need to
什么东西需要7,000鲍勃
bail that means there's either 6999
保释，这意味着有6999
other ones or there's 7,000 other ones
其他的或其他7,000个
and you make seven thousand and one
你赚了七千零一个
depending on how you read that part of
取决于你如何阅读那部分内容
it but the fact is I mean if you're off
它， 但事实是我的意思是，如果你离开
by six thousand 999 you're off I mean
到了六千九九九你是我的意思
that's I mean this is not horseshoes
我的意思是这不是马蹄铁
work you know if you're within a
工作你知道如果你在一个
horseshoe you it still counts
马蹄你仍然很重要
you know this is off I'm the only one
你知道这是关闭我是唯一的一个
left and he wasn't the only one left and
左，他不是唯一的一个左
what is he doing he's centering his
他在做什么他是他的中心
thoughts on himself I testified to you
对自己的想法我 向你作证
when you are depressed you don't think
当你沮丧时，你不会想到
about anybody but yourself you don't
关于任何人， 除了你自己，你没有
want the kids around you don't want the
希望你周围的孩子不要这样
grandkids around you you want your wife
你想要你的妻子在你周围的孙子孙女
around because she takes care of you
因为她照顾你
you know but you're you're thinking
你知道，但你在想
about yourself
关于你自己
why does he run he was afraid for his
为什么他跑他害怕他
life that's why he runs he runs for his
这就是为什么他跑，他跑在他的生活
life I'm the only one left Lord take me
生活我是唯一一个离开主带我的人
home and he's thinking about that now in
家里，他现在正在考虑这个问题
these cases this is not these are not
这些情况下，这是不是这些都是不
the only steps that lead into depression
导致抑郁症的唯一步骤
but they are the ones I think I can
但他们是我认为我能做到的
observe in the life of Elijah but now
在以利亚的生活中观察， 但现在
what does God do because he's the
上帝做了什么，因为他是
counselor in this case and it's critical
在这种情况下顾问，这是至关重要的
to remember that this is something for
要记住，这是后话
you to study because God is the
你学习，因为上帝是
counselor what does God do in this
辅导员上帝在这方面做了什么
situation all you you need to remember
所有你需要记住的情况
he's omniscient and so God doesn't need
他是无所不知的，所以上帝不需要
to get facts from the counsel league
获得从律师联盟事实
because he's God and he already knows
因为他是上帝， 他已经知道了
I'm nationally everything you're gonna
我是全国所有你想要的东西
need to ask a lot of questions according
需要请 根据很多问题
to proverbs 18:13 you don't want to be a
箴言18:13你不想成为一个
fool who answers the matter before he's
在他之前回答此事的傻瓜
heard it
听到了
Jesus is the wonderful counselor so we
耶稣是非常好的顾问， 所以我们
need to pay close attention to how he
需要密切关注他如何
and his father handle this case and so
他父亲处理这个案子等等
as he's doing that what's he first do he
因为他做的是什么，他首先做他
gives his servant rest and not only does
让他的仆人休息而不仅仅是
he give him rest in this situation but
他 在这种情况下让他休息了
it's the opposite of what you could have
这与你可能拥有的相反
expected now mind you you've blown it
我们现在想到你已经吹了它
you didn't even ask my help you all you
你甚至没有让我帮助你
want to come home okay you know I cooked
想回家好吧你知道我煮熟了
the sacrifice on yesterday I can cook
昨天的牺牲我可以做饭
you today but you're glad God doesn't
你今天但是你很高兴上帝没有
think like me isn't it almost
觉得像我这样是不是差不多
blasphemous even for me to say those
亵渎神明甚至让我说出那些
things when you think of the marvels of
当你想到的奇迹时的事情
God the caring God the God who says to
敬畏上帝的上帝是对上帝说的上帝
us cast every burden on me because I
因为我， 我们为我施加了每一个负担
care for you so what does he do well he
关心你，他做得怎么样？
gives him sleep and then he gives rest
让他睡觉然后他休息
so you want to do that
所以你想这样做
give sleep and rest before confrontation
在对抗之前给予睡眠和休息
before dealing with those issues Bible
在处理那些问题圣经之前
says in Psalm 127 2 he gives his beloved
在诗篇127篇2中他说他给了他心爱的人
sleep and then again you know do not
睡觉然后再知道你不知道
extended counseling when the people are
当人们延长辅导
exhausted
累
and they're reacting to you there
他们在那里对你作出反应
irritable they're angry
他们很生气
remember your ability is the first sign
记住你的能力是第一个迹象
of significant sleep loss and again find
显着的睡眠损失再次发现
that question I just read an article
那个问题我刚读了一篇文章
this week by a doctor Whittaker
本周由医生惠特克
everybody needs 7 to 9 hours of sleep
每个人都需要7到9个小时的睡眠时间
you can play with that all you want but
你可以玩所有你想要的但是
every study I have read over the last 40
我在过去的40年里读过的每一项研究
years teaches that you need six to eight
几年教你需要六到八个
glasses of water a day not Coke not
每天 喝杯 水不可乐不行
whatever you need water those are pretty
无论你需要什么水，那些都很漂亮
much medical facts people mess with
很多医疗事实让人搞乱
their sleep patterns all the time and
他们的睡眠模式一直都是
you need to help them get those
你需要帮助他们得到那些
straightened out he gives him physical
理顺他给他身体
nourishment he sends an angel hold this
营养他派天使抱这个
is cool much better than the Ravens I
比乌鸦我好多了
would certainly prefer an angel
肯定会更喜欢天使
delivering one of these cakes and the
提供其中一个蛋糕和
word here is the word for a special cake
这里的单词是一个特殊的蛋糕
this is like my wife's banana bread or
这就像我妻子的香蕉面包或者
even better like her zucchini bread and
甚至更像她的西葫芦面包和
if you haven't ever had my wife's
如果你还没有过我的妻子
zucchini bread you should come visit us
西葫芦面包你应该来看我们
sometime it is good it's a savory cake
有时它很好吃，这是一个美味的蛋糕
and delivered by the Angels you know and
并由你知道的天使提供
so he does this he's ministering to
所以他这样做他伺候
those physical needs and we need to
那些物质需求，我们需要
recognize the angel comes twice so a
认识到天使来了两次这样一个
lack of nourishment can bring on
缺乏营养可以带来
depression it's you read it in the DSM
抑郁症是你在DSM中读到的
for the world recognizes it physical
因为世界认识到它是物理的
weight loss is a factor there and then
减肥是一个因素
God gives his servant proof of his love
上帝赐给他的仆人证明他的爱
in the sleep and he doesn't deal with
在睡梦中，他没有处理
him according to his sins where he's run
根据他的罪行，他在哪里跑
and not I ask for help he hasn't
而不是我求助他没有
recorded us rewarded us according to our
记录我们根据我们的奖励奖励我们
iniquities
罪孽
second Timothy 2:13 if we are faithless
提摩太后书2:13如果我们没有信仰
he remains faithful he can't deny
他仍然忠诚， 他不能否认
himself and so he promises he will
他自己， 所以他承诺，他将
finish the work that he has started in
完成他开始的工作
us and he is the one who will finish
我们和他是谁将完成
that work but you've got to remember
那工作但你必须记住
this
这个
knowing Christ is worth more than
认识基督的价值超过
anything else but you will know him in
别的什么，但你会认识他
the power of the Resurrection and in the
复活的力量和复活的力量
Fellowship of his suffering so you will
他的痛苦的团契，所以你会
know Christ in the Fellowship of
知道基督在团契中
suffering you may go through depression
痛苦你可能会经历抑郁症
you say I have pretty much an upbeat
你说我有一个乐观的态度
personality in the sense I never
从来没有这种意义上的个性
expected ever that I would go through
期待我会经历
the kind of depression I went through I
我经历过的那种抑郁症
was out of work for nine week nine
失业了九个9周
months I thank God for the graciousness
几个月我感谢上帝的恩惠
that the school exercised and the way
学校运用和方式
they handled my situation made it
他们处理我的情况使它
possible for me to keep my job and and
我可以继续工作
continue in that situation and as they
继续在那种情况下和他们一样
showed their love for me and the way
表现出对我 的方式和他们的爱情
Ernie and John the way Wayne sent me a
厄尼和约翰的方式韦恩送我一个
material you know he didn't mention that
你知道他没有提到的材料
he was one of my counselors at a
他是我的一名辅导员
distance when I was going through you
我经过你的距离
know this time of depression I have in
我知道这段时间的抑郁症
my files the things he sent me I believe
我的档案是他寄给我的东西我相信
it was on Psalm 18 and so he gives us
这是在诗篇18篇，所以他给了我们
deserve an awareness of his power and
值得了解他的力量和力量
then that his power in the wind his
然后他的力量在风中他的
power in the earthquake is powered in
地震中的电力被供电
the fire his arm is not short you know
他知道，他的手臂不短
God is at work in that circumstance and
在这种情况下，上帝正在工作
he is working for good in that and you
他和你在一起工作
got to give this person hope because
得到这个人的希望，因为
they've lost hope and you have to keep
他们失去了希望，你必须坚持下去
telling them the truth whether they are
告诉他们他们 是否真相
kind of accepting it at that point or
那种接受它或者
not and so you have to continue to work
不是，所以你必须继续工作
in that area you got to get them to put
在那个区域你必须得到它们
their mind on Jehovah Jireh the God who
他们对耶和华以勒神记谁
provides rather than on those things
提供而不是那些东西
they're facing at that time a powerful
他们当时面临着强大的力量
passage in this and putting their minds
通过这个和他们的想法
on God and his power is the passage in
在上帝和他的力量是通道
1st Peter 5b through 11 and you know in
第一个彼得5b到11，你知道
that passage Peter tells us you know
那段经文彼得告诉我们你知道
that it's time to get dressed and as a
现在是时候穿好衣服了
Christian how do you get dressed well
基督教你如何穿好衣服好
you're gonna clothe yourself in humility
你会谦卑地穿上自己
now in get
现在在得到
dress and it says you younger men
穿着，它说你年轻的男人
likewise be subject to your elders and
同样受你的长辈和
all of you clothed yourselves with
你们所有人都穿着自己
humility toward one another for God is
上帝对彼此的谦卑是
opposed to the proud but gives grace to
反对骄傲的人，赐恩给
the humble
谦虚
so therefore humble yourself under the
因此，在自己的谦卑之下
mighty hand of God that he may exalt you
上帝的大能之手 ，他可以高举你
at the profit time casting all your
在利润时间铸造所有你的
anxiety on him because he cares for you
对他的焦虑， 因为他关心你
so be of sober spirit be on the alert
所以要清醒精神提高警觉
your adversary the devil prowls around
你的敌人魔鬼四处游荡
like a roaring lion seeking someone to
就像咆哮的狮子寻找某人一样
but devour you know he's coming across
但吞噬你，你知道他正在遇到
like the the threatening Jezebel seeking
喜欢威胁的耶洗别寻求
someone to devour but resist him firm in
有人吞噬，但坚决抵抗他
your faith knowing that the same
你的信心知道相同
experiences of suffering are being
痛苦的经历正在发生
accomplished by your brethren but after
由你的弟兄们完成但是之后
you have suffered for a little while the
你曾经遭受过一段时间的痛苦
God of all Grace who called you to his
所有格雷斯神 谁叫你到他
eternal glory in Christ will himself
基督里永远的荣耀就是他自己
perfect you and confirm you and
完善你并确认你和
strengthen you and establish you
加强你，建立你
remember that idea in the Greek what do
记得希腊人的想法是做什么的
you do you pile up words these words are
你做你堆积起来的话，这些话是
very similar but they mean and what he's
非常相似，但他们的意思是什么，他是什么
trying to say is listen after you've
试着说是在你以后听
suffered a little while and tell me this
遭受了一段时间并告诉我这一点
when it when you're in depression
什么时候你在抑郁症
doesn't feel like a little while it
感觉不像是一点点
feels like the day will never end then
感觉这一天将永远不会再结
you don't want to go to sleep because
你不想去睡觉因为
the night will never end because you
夜晚永远不会因为你而结束
know you're not gonna sleep and you're
知道你不会睡觉，而你却是
gonna be awake all night and you've
整晚都会醒来，你已经
tried philippians 4 or 4 to 9 and you
试过菲律宾4或4到9和你
and you've learned that and you've given
而且你已经了解到并且你已经给了
that to hundreds of people in counseling
这对数百人的咨询
and now as you try to say it over it
现在当你试图说出来的时候
doesn't seem to make any difference and
似乎没有任何区别
whereas before when you've dealt with
而在此之前，当你处理
this you would see relief immediately
这会让你立刻感到宽慰
this time you're not seeing any relief
这次你没有看到任何缓解
immediately but you must keep practicing
马上但你必须继续练习
what is right because in the light of
什么是正确的，因为根据
eternity it is a little while and it
永恒它是一段时间而且它
will pass you got to talk to yourself so
会过去你这么谈谈自己
why are you despair within me hope in
你为什么在我内心绝望
God you will yet praise Him and stick by
上帝你会赞美他并坚持下去
that person you as a counselor and
那个人你作为顾问和
continue to say the truth when you don't
当你不这样做时，继续说实话
look it doesn't look like you're seeing
看起来它看起来并不像你看到的那样
any results read about how Newton
任何结果都是关于牛顿的
followed copper all through his life and
在他的生命和
even in his death calper was not sure of
甚至在他的死亡中，calper也不确定
his salvation
他的救赎
I read his hymns I believe that nobody
我读了他的赞美诗我相信没有人
could write that kind of a hand
可以写那种手
unless they knew Christ but there are
除非他们认识基督， 但有
issues with depression that we don't
抑郁症的问题，我们没有
understand but we do understand this God
明白， 但我们明白这个上帝
is in your problem and he's in it for
是你的问题，他是在它
good and the Word of God said after you
善良，上帝的话在你之后说
have suffered for a little while the God
曾经遭受过一段时间的上帝
of all grace the God who calls you to
所有恩典都是召唤你的上帝
his eternal glory in Christ will himself
他在基督里永恒的荣耀就是他自己
perfect you and confirm you and
完善你并确认你和
strengthen you and establish you to him
加强你，并建立你
be Dominion forever and ever you got to
永远是自治领，你必须
put your your hope in those promises and
把你的希望寄托在那些承诺上
you got to get dressed and what you
你得穿好衣服，你是什么
dress yourself with is humility you have
穿着自己是你的谦逊
to humble yourself under the mighty hand
在强大的手下谦卑自己
of God you don't know what God's doing
上帝， 你不知道上帝在做什么
you don't know all of his reasoning you
你不知道他的所有推理你
can't understand why you don't like your
无法理解你为什么不喜欢你
wife's cooking anymore when she's one of
当她是其中一个时，妻子正在做饭
the best cooks in the universe you don't
你不是宇宙中最好的厨师
know why you're doing these things you
知道你为什么要做这些事情
got to cast your burden on him and why
我要把负担放在他身上，为什么呢
because he cares for you and you've got
因为他关心你，而你却得到了
a lookout for the devil he wants to
寻找他想要的魔鬼
devour you just read job chapter 1 and 2
吞噬你，你只需阅读第1章和第2章
and see what he does when he gets
看看他得到了什么
permission from God to do it he has to
从上帝允许这样做，他必须
have permission you need to resist the
有权限你需要抵制
devil how firm in your faith
魔鬼你的信仰有多坚定
confident in your faith just look around
对你的信仰充满信心只是环顾四周
everybody is suffering just scratch the
每个人都受苦受伤
surface just go to the internet and read
表面只是去互联网阅读
about the suffering in Sudan or
关于苏丹或苏丹的苦难
Afghanistan or any other place and it's
阿富汗或任何其他地方，它
just though for a little while and
虽然有一段时间了
that's God's truth and then the God of
这是上帝的真理，然后是上帝的真理
Grace who called you he himself will
格蕾丝自己会打电话给你
keep your trial short and he will bring
保持你的审判时间短，他会带来
it through he will perfect you he will
它通过他将完善你他会
confirm you he will strengthen you he
确认你他会加强你
will establish you he's going to do that
将建立你他要做到这一点
and so in that next sense he gives them
所以在下一个意义上他给了他们
a vision of his presence he passes by he
他的存在的愿景，他经过他
spoke in the gentle blowing wind and
在温柔的吹风中说话
then you know God is going to speak to
那么你知道上帝会说话
us and we can't be taken out of his hand
我们和我们不能脱离他的手
there's nowhere you can go from God's
没有什么地方你可以从神的去
presence you got to remind the person
在场， 你必须提醒这个人
that he's guarding your going out and
他正在守着你的外出
your coming in
你的进来
he gives his servant a proper
他给了他的仆人一个合适的人
perspective on the facts you're not the
透视你不是的事实
only one left you need to realize the
只有一个你需要实现的
suffering that job went through and how
痛苦的工作经历了怎么样
job responded we're all called to suffer
工作回应我们都被称为受苦
for Christ those are perspectives on the
对于基督来说，这些是关于
facts that that the depressed person
那个郁闷的人的事实
need you need to explain that the wicked
需要你解释那个恶人
are not getting away with anything
没有逃避任何事情
the fact is their judgment is coming and
事实是他们的判断即将来临
it is sure God explains that in 1917 to
可以肯定上帝在1917年解释说
Elisha we're told that in Romans 12 and
以利沙，我们被告知在罗马书 12
all Christians need to expect they're
所有基督徒都需要期待他们
going to go through suffering and then
然后 经历苦难
he gives his servant an assignment he
他给了他的仆人一份任务
puts him back to work tells him to go
让他回去工作告诉他去
back into the situation he's going to
回到他要去的情况
anoint hazel Jehu and Elisha and judge
anel hazelJehu和Elisha和法官
sin so he gets him moving so it's
因此， 他让他移动，所以它是
important to get that depressed moving
让这种沮丧感动变得很重要
person moving in the right direction and
人在正确的方向前进和
here are four final steps you need to
这里有四个步骤，最终你需要
believe God you need to examine your
相信上帝，你需要检查你的
heart for any issues of repentance you
任何忏悔问题的心脏
need to talk to yourself need to trust
需要自言自语需要信任
yourself to fellow believers and you
你自己和信徒以及你
need to just do right by faith now we've
我们现在需要凭信心做正确的事
had to rush at the end of this if you go
曾在本月底 匆匆 ，如果你去
to Antioch Antioch Bible Church
到安提阿安提阿圣经教会
Johannesburg South Africa that's the
南非约翰内斯堡是这样的
last place I was able to give the three
最后一个地方，我能够给这三个
hours you can download all three hours
小时，你可以下载所有三个小时
if you want to fill in on this it's a
如果你想填写这是一个
Antioch Bible Church Johannesburg South
安提阿圣经教会约翰内斯堡南
Africa and go to their site and then you
非洲，去他们的网站，然后你
can do sermons and go back to June and
可以做布道，然后回到六月和
you should be able to pick up on the
你应该可以挑上的
sermons or the seminar I did there on
布道或我在那里做的研讨会
depression I'm sorry I had to rush this
抑郁症我很抱歉我不得不赶紧过去
but here's the idea you tell them you
但这是你告诉他们的想法
must believe God not your feelings
必须相信上帝而不是你的感受
you tell them examine their heart are
你告诉他们审视自己的心脏是
their issues that have drawn them into
他们的问题已经吸引他们
this the circle of depression gets worse
这个抑郁症的圈子变得更糟
when you do not respond biblically and
当你没有圣经和圣经的回应
you respond non biblically and if
你非圣经地回应，如果
they've maybe already been in that
他们可能已经在那里了
pattern and that may be the whole
模式，这可能是整体
solution
解
as they just start to do right and the
因为他们刚开始做对了
depression lives when Caine is depressed
当Caine沮丧时，抑郁症就会消失
and his countenance has fallen God just
他的面容已经堕落了上帝
says to him do right and your
对他说对你做对了
countenance will lift you won't be
面容会举起你不会
depressed and then teach them to talk to
郁闷，然后教他们 说话
themselves talk to their soul and speak
他们自己与自己的灵魂交谈并说话
harshly to their soul soul listen to me
他们的灵魂狠狠地听着我的灵魂
trust in God we need to do that trust
相信上帝， 我们需要做到这种信任
yourself to follow believers do you know
你知道，自己跟随信徒
are you with do you have friends who if
你有朋友吗？
you end up in this situation will speak
你最终会在这种情况下说话
to you the truth and tell you the truth
给你真相并告诉你真相
that you need to hear and then again
你需要再听一遍
just do right by faith I close with this
只是凭着信心做正确的事情
illustration I'm in church in the middle
插图我在教堂中间
of this depression
这种抑郁症
they're serving communion Jason Horton
他们正在为圣餐Jason Horton服务
is the elder on my side who's serving
是我身边的老人谁在服务
communion and he's getting closer he
圣餐，他越来越近了
also writes my checks because he's the
还写我的支票， 因为他是
chief financial officer at the college
学院的首席财务官
that I work at and they're taking
我在工作，他们正在服用
communion and I'm thinking I don't even
圣餐，我想我甚至都没有
know if I'm a believer I don't know if
知道我是不是一个信徒我不知道是否
I'm elect I come to church and I don't
我当选我来教堂而不是
have any emotion I hear the truth of the
有任何感情，我听到了真相
word of God i hear the blessing of the
上帝的话我听到了祝福
tremendous sacrifice of christ for me
为我做出了巨大的基督牺牲
and my soul seems dead within me am I
而我的灵魂似乎死在我里面
gonna take communion if you take
如果你采取会采取圣餐
communion you take it on worthily you
圣餐你值得拥有它
eat nation unto yourself well what am I
为了自己 吃国家 ，我是什么
gonna do and fine I thought I believe
要做得好，我以为我相信
this is truth if I am saved I am saved
如果我得救，这就是事实我得救了
by the blood of Christ I did declare my
借着基督的血， 我确实宣告了我的
faith in Christ when I was 13 years old
我13 岁时对基督的信仰
I did believe I was saved for thirty
我确实相信我得救了三十岁
five forty five fifty five years you
五十五五十五年你
know I thought I was walking with God
知道我以为我和上帝同行
and if somebody else asked me today how
如果有人今天问我怎么样
do you get saved I would show them the
你得救了我会告诉他们的
Romans Road okay Lord I'm gonna take
Romans Road好吧主我要去
communion on the basis of this is what I
基于此的共融就是我
would confess to anyone this is how you
会向任何人承认这就是你
get saved I know
我知道了
no FIM say Lord but I believe it's right
没有FIM说主，但我相信这是对的
to confess this it's the only means by
承认这一点，是由唯一手段
which you can be saved by the body and
你可以通过身体保存
blood of Christ so I took communion and
基督的血，所以我采取了圣餐和
thankful now that I take that with a
谢天谢地，我接受了
whole different motion and that when we
整个不同的运动， 当我们
sing in Christ alone I understand that I
只在基督里唱歌， 我明白我
am in Christ alone and I'm only saved in
我独自在基督里，我只是被拯救了
Christ alone and all those feelings can
只有基督和所有这些感情都可以
go but you can't get somebody out of the
去，但你不能让别人出来的
hand of the Good Shepherd got to give
好牧人的手必须给予
this truth and all the truth of the word
这个真理和这个词的所有真相
but remember to measure it in the
但记得要衡量它的
context of the way God does giving rest
上帝确实给予休息的方式的背景
giving nourishment getting them on track
提供营养让他们走上正轨
in those ways as well for the wise and
在那些方面以及智慧和
omniscient counselor started that way
无所不知的辅导员就是这样开始的
with his prophet Elijah
与他的先知以利亚
you
您